mediapss.com 2016-10-26

# Media Pass

## 1\. Introduction

M. Advisors UК Privacy Policy

Effective as of August 25, 2015

This online privacy policy describes the types of information M. Advisors UК ("we"/"us"/"our"). Gathers from those persons visiting the Internet website www.mediapss.com (the Site) and how we use that information. By accessing this Site, you agree to be bound by the Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use this Site. M. Advisors UК reserves the right to modify this Privacy Policy from time to time. Changes to the Privacy Policy will be posted on the Site and the effective date of the most recent version of the Privacy Policy will be modified to reflect the effective date of the most recent version.

## 2\. GENERAL

We may collect two types of information from users of our Site: personally identifiable information (such as name, e-mail and IP address) and aggregate information (such as frequency of visits to the Site, search terms entered, Site pages most frequently accessed, browser type, etc.).

## 3\. COLLECTION AND USE OF PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

Information We Collect

M. Advisors UК may collect the following information from or about you:

Information You Provide To Us. We collect information you provide to us. For instance, when you register to use the M. Advisors UK Services, we collect your name, email address, birth date, and gender. If you are a paying subscriber, we also collect your credit card information, which may include your billing address and zip code. In addition, M. Advisors UK may collect information you provide to us when you respond to surveys, contact M. Advisors UK through customer service or by other means, or participate in promotions that M. Advisors UK may offer from time to time.

Usage and Log Data. We collect information when you use the M. Advisors UK Services or view M. Advisors UK advertising outside of the M. Advisors UK Services. This information may include your IP address, device and software characteristics (such as type and operating system), location, activity on the M. Advisors UK Services including title selections and watch history, page views, ad data, referral URLs, network state, device identifiers or other unique identifiers such as advertising identifiers (e.g., "ad-ID" or "IDFA"), and carrier information.

Data Collected Through Cookies and Similar Technologies. Like many online services, we use various technologies to collect usage data and store preferences. One such technology is called a cookie. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your computer's hard disk. We may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with the M. Advisors UK Services or M. Advisors UK advertising published outside of the M. Advisors UK Services and to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on the M. Advisors UK Services. This allows us to improve the M. Advisors UK Services. Also, we may create a unique device or user ID for you and store it in a cookie so we can recognize you and customize your experience based on your preferences.

We may collect information through other kinds of local storage (also referred to as "Flash cookies") and HTML5 local storage, including in connection with features such as volume/mute settings for the Video Player. Because these technologies are similar to browser cookies, they are sometimes called "browser cookies," even though they may be stored in different parts of your computer.

Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by changing its settings, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. For information about disabling cookies or deleting information contained in Flash Cookies, please click here. Please note that disabling cookies or deleting information contained in cookies or Flash Cookies may interfere with the performance and features of the M. Advisors UK Services, including the Video Player. For example, we may not be able to store any of your preferences or login information or customize the Content to your viewing habits.

In addition to cookies, we may use other technologies such as web beacons or pixel tags, which can be embedded in web pages, videos, or emails, to collect certain types of information from your browser, check whether you have viewed a particular web page or email message, and determine, among other things, the time and date on which you viewed the Content, the IP address of your computer, and the URL of the web page from which the Content was viewed.

The use of these various technologies in connection with advertising on the M. Advisors UK Services is explained further below.

Social Networking Data. If you choose to log-in, access or otherwise connect to the M. Advisors UK Services, or contact M. Advisors UK, through a social networking service (such as Facebook), we may collect your user ID and user name associated with that social networking service, as well as any information you make public using that social networking service. We may also collect information you have authorized the social networking service to share with us (such as your user ID, public profile information, email address, birthday, friends list, and pages you have "liked").

Third-Party Data. We may collect information about you from other sources, such as data aggregators, public databases, and our business partners. This may include information about your interests, demographic data, purchasing behavior, and your activities online (such as websites visited and advertisements viewed).

We may combine the information we collect from or about you and use it in the manner described in this Privacy Policy.

## 4\. COLLECTION AND USE OF IP ADDRESSES

In addition, we collect IP addresses to obtain aggregate information on the Site. An IP address is a number assigned to your computer by a web server when you are on the web. When you are on our Site, we have a back-end server that logs your computer’s IP address. We only use the information we find out from tracking IP addresses in the aggregate, such as how many users entered a specific area of our Site, and not to track a specific IP address to identify an individual user. However, we may use such information to identify a user if we feel that there are or may be safety and/or security issues or to comply with legal requirements.

## 5\. SHARING, SELLING, AND TRADING PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION COLLECTED ONLINE WITH THIRD PARTIES

We will not share, rent, sell or otherwise disclose personally identifiable information collected on the Site to third parties for such parties own marketing and promotional purposes.

In the following circumstances we may share or transfer personally identifiable information collected on the Site to unrelated third parties: (i) to comply with a legal requirement, judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on us, (ii) to investigate a possible crime, such as fraud or identity theft; (iii) in connection with the sale, purchase, merger, reorganization, liquidation or dissolution of our company; or (iv) when we believe it is appropriate to do so to protect the rights, property, or safety of visitors to our Site or other persons.

## 6\. SHARING, SELLING AND TRADING AGGREGATE INFORMATION COLLECTED ONLINE WITH THIRD PARTIES

We may sell, share or trade compiled aggregate information relating to activity on the Site, with third parties for marketing, research and other purposes. No single person can be identified by such aggregate information.

## 7\. Third-Party Advertising, Including Opt-Out Options

Viewing Ads. When you view an advertisement, whether or not you click on it, the advertiser, advertising technology companies, and service providers that perform advertising-related services for us and our business partners may collect some information from or about you. The information practices of these third parties are governed by their own privacy policies and are not covered by this Privacy Policy. Please be aware that M. Advisors UK does not notify you when you have chosen to click through to another website or property when using the M. Advisors UK Services. We recommend that you familiarize yourself with the privacy policies of such websites or properties to determine how they handle any information they separately collect from you.

## 8\. Other Websites, Platforms and Applications

M. Advisors UK service may be provided through platforms or contain links to sites operated by third parties whose policies regarding the handling of information may differ from ours. For example, you may be able to access the M. Advisors UK service through platforms such as gaming systems, smart TVs, mobile devices, set top boxes and a number of other Internet connected devices. These websites and platforms have separate and independent privacy or data policies, privacy statements, notices and terms of use, which we recommend you read carefully. In addition, you may encounter third party applications that interact with the M. Advisors UK service.

## 9\. CHILDREN AND PRIVACY

We are concerned about the safety of children when they use the Internet, and realize that children may not understand all the provisions of our Privacy Policy or make informed decisions about the choices that are made available to adult users of the Site. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time with their children online and to be familiar with the sites their children visit. Our Site is not directed towards children under the age of thirteen (13). We will not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen (13). If we become aware that a user is under the age of thirteen (13) and has provided personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent, we will remove his or her personally identifiable information from our files.

## 10\. SECURITY

We restrict access to personally identifiable information collected from visitors of our Site to our employees who need to know that information in order to provide services to you. In addition, we make reasonable efforts to follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personally identifiable information submitted to us. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, however, is 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

IN NO EVENT WILL M. Advisors UK, OUR OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, LICENSORS, SUPPLIERS OR ANY PARTY INVOLVED IN CREATING, PRODUCING OR DELIVERING THIS SITE (RELEASED PARTIES) BE LIABLE IN ANY MANNER WHATSOEVER FOR ANY DAMAGES OF ANY KIND, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, SPECIAL OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES ARISING OUT OF: (I) THIS SITE, YOUR ACCESS, USE OR INABILITY TO USE THIS SITE; (II) ANY FAILURE OR PERFORMANCE, ERROR, OMISSION, INTERRUPTION, DEFECT, DELAY IN OPERATION OR TRANSMISSION, COMPUTER VIRUS OR LINE OR SYSTEM FAILURE (INCLUDING LOSS PROFITS, LOSS OF BUSINESS OR DATA, BUSINESS INTERRUPTION, AND DAMAGES THAT RESULT FROM INACCURACY OF THE INFORMATION OR INCONVENIENCE, DELAY, OR LOSS OF THE USE OF THE SITE); (III) PERSONAL INJURY OR PROPERTY DAMAGE, OF ANY NATURE WHATSOEVER, RESULTING FROM YOUR ACCESS TO AND USE OF THE SITE, (IV) ANY UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO OR USE OF OUR SECURE SERVERS AND/OR ANY AND ALL PERSONAL IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION STORED THEREIN, (V) ANY BUGS, VIRUSES, TROJAN HORSES, OR THE LIKE, WHICH MAY BE TRANSMITTED TO OR THROUGH THE SITE BY ANY THIRD PARTY.

THE FOREGOING LIMITATIONS APPLY WHETHER THE ALLEGED LIABILITY IS BASED ON CONTRACT, TORT, NEGLIGENCE STRICT LIABILITY OR ANY OTHER BASIS, EVEN THE RELEASED PARTIES OR ANY OTHER PARTY HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.

BECAUSE SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, THE RELEASED PARTIES LIABILITY IN SUCH JURISDICTIONS SHALL BE LIMITED TO THE EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW.

## 11\. LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES 

This Site may contain links to websites operated by other people or companies. Those websites may have their own privacy policy or no privacy policy at all. We do not control the content of those websites and take no responsibility for their content, nor should it be implied that we endorse or otherwise recommend such sites or the products or services offered. We encourage you to review the privacy policies and terms of use of any third party sites. We provide the links solely for the convenience of our visitors.

## 12\. BUSINESS TRANSFERS

In the future we may sell, merge or otherwise reorganize our business. M. Advisors UK reserves the right to transfer and disclose personally identifiable information in this circumstance, but data collected by M. Advisors UK will be governed by the same privacy policy that existed prior to any change in business conditions unless you consent to the new privacy policy.

## 13\. CHANGES TO THIS POLICY

We reserve the right to update or modify this Policy, at any time and without prior notice, by posting the revised version of this Policy on our Site.

## 14\. CORRECTIONS/INFORMATION REMOVAL/OPT-OUT

If your name, e-mail address or other personally identifiable information collected during the registration process changes, you may update, correct or omit the relevant information by contacting us at support@mediapss.com

If you prefer not to receive marketing e-mails from us, please click on the unsubscribe link within any marketing e-mail you receive from us. Please note that such requests may take up to ten (10) days to become effective.

Sending postal mail to: M. Advisors UK Privacy Officer

M. Advisors UK

## 15\. CONTACT US

If you have questions regarding this Privacy Policy or the information collection and dissemination practices of this Site, please contact us at: M. Advisors UK. If you have questions regarding Media Pass, please contact our support via phone or write an email to support@mediapss.com.
